reviewgamezone.com 2017-07-16

# Privacy Policy

Effective Date: February 20, 2017

1\. Acceptance 

We have created this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) because we value users’ privacy. The Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you, or that you may provide, when you access ReviewGameZone.com (the “Site”). Holocene Holdings LLC, a New York company, owns and operates the Site. This Policy does not apply to information collected by any third party, including through any external website that may link to or be accessible from the Site. Please check directly with each such third party to avoid unfair surprises and misunderstandings. 

Your use of this Site constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you may not use our Site. This Policy may change from time to time, and the date of last update is indicated at the top of this page. Your continued use of this Site after we revise this Policy is deemed to be acceptance of the revisions, so please check this page from time to time for updates. 

2\. What information we collect 

The Site does not collect personal information unless an adult user chooses to register an account. Information collected from registered accounts is not shared, sold, posted or otherwise disseminated to other third parties, unless required by law. We may collect several types of information from users of our Site, including the following: 

a. Personal Data: Name, address, IP addresses. 

b. Voluntary Data: Information you voluntarily provide to the Site or when you contact us for any reason. We collect this information: 

c. Directly from you when you provide it to us (e.g. when you contact us for any reason). 

d. Automatically as you navigate through the Site. 

3\. How we use your information 

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information: 

a. To provide the services you requested. 

b. To notify you about changes to our Site or any services we offer or provide though it. 

c. To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights. 

d. In any other way we may describe when you provide the information. 

4\. Disclosure of your information 

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this Policy: 

a. To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. 

b. To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business. 

c. To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Site's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information about our Site users is among the assets transferred. 

d. We may, without restriction, disclose aggregated information about our users and information that does not identify any individual. 

e. For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information. We may also disclose your personal information: 

f. To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request. 

g. If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Site, its users or others. 

5\. Data security 

Personal information you provide to us is stored on a password protected server. However, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Site because any transmission of information over the Internet has its inherent risks. Additionally, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information (including but not limited to: user name, email address, password, name) once submitted to our servers. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You are responsible for keeping your login credentials, if any, confidential. 

6\. Children’s Privacy 

a. Policy for Minors. Use of any section of the Site by minors is prohibited without permission by a parent or legal guardian of the minor. Minors are not permitted to submit personal information at any time to this Site other than their first name and first two letters of the their last names provided they are 13 years old or older and their teacher requested said information to be used via the statistical collection portion of the Site. It is the teacher’s responsibility to assure all rules are followed by their students while using this Site once parent or guardian permission is granted. ReviewGameZone.com does not knowingly accept, print or process information submitted by minors under 13 years old, and cannot be held responsible for such actions. 

b. Policy for Adults. Do not attempt to make contact with any minor using portions of this Site. You should not voluntarily disclose personal information. ReviewGameZone.com cannot be held responsible for situations that arise from such situations where personal information is disclosed while using areas on this Site. PLEASE NOTE: upon giving your child consent to access the Internet; they are being exposed to certain material that may not be appropriate for minors. They are also being exposed to areas where they may have communication with adults, where personal information such as phone numbers and addresses, could be voluntarily revealed. Please talk to your children about these areas, before you grant them consent. ReviewGameZone.com cannot be held responsible for situations that arise from such situations where personal information is disclosed while using this Site. 

7\. Cookies 

a. Use of Cookies. Cookies are small bits of data sent from a web server to your web browser, and then stored on your hard drive. ReviewGameZone.com uses cookies for statistical analysis of users. Information collected includes, but is not limited to: IP address, browser type, operating system specifications, date & time of entry and exit of site. This information is collected to make your web-surfing experience easier. ReviewGameZone.com reserves the right to use this information in circumstances where law enforcement agencies, court orders, or subpoenas, or any other circumstance that is part of a criminal investigation arises from use of this site. You have the ability to disable cookies from your web-browser. By doing this, some sections of this site, may not function properly. 

b. Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

8\. Accessing and correcting your personal information 

Please contact us by using the form located here: http://reviewgamezone.com/site-help/ to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us or to ask questions about this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to refuse a request if we believe it would violate any law or cause the information to be incorrect. 

Any claim relating to ReviewGameZone.com shall be governed by the laws of the State of New York without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
